(Howard:)Plus it was the only boys' large
they had.
(Raj:)I'm sorry. This does not look like Texas.
Where's the tumbleweeds?
(Raj:)-Where's the saloons?
-Saloons?
(Raj:)Like in the movies I saw growing up.
You know, uh, 4 for Texas,
Yellow Rose of Texas.
This neighborhood
is more Texas Chainsaw Massacre.
(Raj:)I was really hoping to see a cattle drive.
(Leonard:)What can I tell you?
(Leonard:)They probably have steaks on sale
at that big-ass Costco over there.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
(Leonard:)Will you please take that stupid hat off?
No, I wanna blend in.
(Raj:)To what? Toy Story?
(Mrs Cooper:)Hi, boys.
(Howard:)-Howdy, ma'am.
-Howdy to you too. You got here quick.
(Leonard:)-We took the redeye.
-Come on in.
(Howard:)Thank you kindly.
(Mrs Cooper:)-Can I get you something to drink?
-No, thank you.